Will Irvin

Charlotte, NC 28205 | Phone: 704-796-2523 | Email: will.irvin18@gmail.com Linkedin | Github | Portfolio

SUMMARY

I am a Full-Stack web developer with almost 7 years experience in customer service. The amount of time spent interacting with customers, and fellow workers has made me extremely well versed in communication and I love learning things about people. I have a deep love and understanding for graphics, art, and UI. I work extremely well in a team environment with plenty of communication, and other minds interested in bouncing off ideas.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.Js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, React, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Sequelize, Firebase, Handlebars, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, Media Queries, APIs, Heroku, Command-Line

Projects

Findaband | Front-End Developer | Deployed Link: Findaband

Code: Code

Website Developed By Myself and a couple of other guys as a project for school

- Role: Responsible for the jQuery code hitting API and generating content
- **Utilized**: HTML5, CSS3, bandsintown api, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js

Heres The Plan | Front-End Developer | Deployed Link: Heres the Plan

Code: Code

Website Developed By Myself and 4 other people for school

- **Role**: Responsible for most of the UI and color schemes, worked very heavily with react and bootstrap to make almost everything
- **Utilized**: HTML5, CSS3, React.js, React, Bootstrap, jQuery, Yarn

Eat The Burger | Front-End Developer | Deployed Link: Eat the Burger

Code: Code

This was a simple website I single-handedly designed for a homework assignment. It utilizes database persistence to keep track of burgers and whether they are "eaten"

- **Role**: I was responsible for all the front and back-end code for this assignment
- Utilized: HTML5, CSS3, HandleBars, MySQL, MySQL workbench, Node.js, Javascript

Will Irvin, Page 2

EXPERIENCE

Central Coffee Company; Charlotte, NC

06/2016 - 12/2017

Lead Barista & Trainer (03/2011 - 05/2015)

Was in charge of register, making drinks, interacting with customers, as well as leading a team and training new hires.

- Worked hard with a team of people, a lot of the time while training
- Consistently handled cash with care and communicated with people constantly.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte, NC Full Stack Web Development | Coding Certificate | 2019

A 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL.